{
    "unit1": [{
            "question": "100 + (-50)",
            "answer": "50"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 + (-50)",
            "answer": "-40"
        },
        {
            "question": "100 + (-500)",
            "answer": "-400"
        },
        {
            "question": "1000 - (-50)",
            "answer": "1050"
        },
        {
            "question": "100 - (-50)",
            "answer": "150"
        },
        {
            "question": "100 + (-50)",
            "answer": "50"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 + (-50)",
            "answer": "-40"
        },
        {
            "question": "100 + (-500)",
            "answer": "-400"
        },
        {
            "question": "1000 - (-50)",
            "answer": "1050"
        },
        {
            "question": "100 - (-50)",
            "answer": "150"
        }

    ],
    "unit2": [{
            "question": "100 x (-50)",
            "answer": "-5000"
        },
        {
            "question": "10 / (-50)",
            "answer": "-0.2"
        },
        {
            "question": "100 x (-500)",
            "answer": "-50000"
        },
        {
            "question": "1000 x (-50)",
            "answer": "-50000"
        },
        {
            "question": "100 / (-50)",
            "answer": "-2"
        },
        {
            "question": "100 x (-50)",
            "answer": "-5000"
        }

    ]

}